creditgate.com 2017-02-24

# Privacy - Business Reports and Information

**  
General**  
This statement sets out our Privacy Policy and explains what personal information we collect from users of our website and what we do with that information. If you have any queries about this policy or our information practices, please contact us using the details given at the end of the policy. 

**  
Consent**  
By using this website you signify that you have consented to our collecting and using the personal information that you provide to us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You will also be deemed to have read and accepted this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and, if we do so, your continued use of the website will be taken as acceptance of any such change. Therefore, we advise you to check this policy on a regular basis. 

**  
Data Collection and Use**  
This Policy applies to all information we receive from you, whether you are registering on our website or ordering any of our products. During the course of your use of this website, Creditgate will collect two types of information:

(i) Aggregated Information - This website automatically gathers certain statistical information such as the number and frequency of visitors. This information is only used in the aggregate and individuals cannot be identified from it. This aggregated information helps us to measure how individuals use the website and our services so that we can continually improve them.

(ii) Personal Information - Creditgate requires personal information from you, such as name and e-mail address, in order for us to perform the services offered by the site and to fulfil your requests. Some of this information is voluntary and the compulsory fields are clearly marked on the form. On occasion, Creditgate may also collect additional personal information from you on a voluntary basis. This personal information may be used in a number of ways:

  1. Identifying potential customers or subscribers. 
  2. As part of the account opening process for new customers, including verifying your identity and carrying out a credit check on you.
  3. Providing you with the services that you have requested. 
  4. We may from time to time send promotional e-mails to you with information about our products and services. If you do not wish to receive such information please send an e-mail to marketing@creditgate.com. 
  5. We may contact you via post, e-mail or telephone in relation to the administration of your account or the provision of your service. 
  6. We may access and disclose personal information about you if you breach this Privacy Policy, and/or to comply with applicable laws, court orders and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself and/or its users. 
  7. We reserve the right to sell the database related to this website (including personal data relating to you) to a third party if we sell, assign or transfer the assets of our business. 
  8. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with 3rd parties. 

We take all reasonable precautions to ensure that outside parties or affiliated companies are aware of our Privacy Policy and that they will treat the personally identifiable information in a similar manner.

**  
Cookies**  
Creditgate uses cookies for collecting user information from this website.

For your information, a cookie is a small piece of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used to make the link between you and the information you have provided to the website, to identify users and personalise their visit by customising web pages for each user. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies although you do not have to. 

Please note if you disable cookies from your browser you may not be able to access certain features of a particular website.

**  
Information Security**  
Creditgate recognises the importance of secure online transactions and takes measures to protect the privacy of information provided to us. We have strict security and confidentiality procedures covering the storage and disclosure of information to maintain its confidentiality, to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

**  
Contact Details**  
If you have any queries about our Privacy Policy or our information practices, please e-mail us at marketing@creditgate.com.

All website material is owned by Creditgate. There must be no reproduction of any of this material without the prior consent of Creditgate. Any use of this website or any statement made by a third party or registrant is their opinion and does not represent the opinion of Creditgate.
